<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on tobeif-DTU</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/publications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on tobeif-DTU</description>
    <image>
      <title>tobeif-DTU</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/images/tobeif.png</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/images/tobeif.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.8</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Our Research</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/research/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;research-in-advanced-engineering-design&#34;&gt;Research in Advanced Engineering Design&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The objective of my research is to widen the applicability of detailed engineering and optimization knowledge in earlier design stages to allow for better informed (design) decision making when conceptualizing and developing robust physical assemblies. Fundamental to this work is the exploration of new product configurations based on the developed theory of design trade-offs, i.e., contradicting requirements or constraints that drastically limit the attainable design space and often result in a reduced window for allowable variation. This idea interfaces well with approaches in the field of material design for energy systems, development of pharmaceutical manufacturing equipment, and digital twin approaches (areas that are explored in an interdisciplinary approach at DTU / see also list of research collaborations). Lastly, my ambition is to keep this research industrially relevant throughout continuous industrial collaboration and to systematically incorporate it into undergraduate and post graduate education, in order to enable students, PhDs, and design practitioners to solve the today’s challenges and to shape engineering design practices for the future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
